well well well what's going on guys
we are starting off today's video a
little bit different because uh
we've got a package that has arrived
let's get this sucker unboxed
[Music]
wow
what's up guys welcome back to yet
another great
product review for you on the channel
here today we are going to take a look
at
the ld
maui 44 g2
guys i've been waiting to do this video
for quite some time but the time is here
so let's get right into it the ld my 44
g2 system is a column array speaker
system that is like no other system that
i probably have dealt with ever now you
guys know that i use qsc
for my current setup and adding these
speakers has been nothing
shy of amazing these guys don't take up
nearly as much space they give you some
great lows and some amazing highs now
what you see in front of you is pretty
much how the system comes i mean you
have your subwoofer you also have two of
your columns which one serves as just a
cabinet to get the actual speakers up
high and guys you ready for this the
other one is just a line of speakers
that's right this whole post right here
is a line of speakers all the power and
everything comes from the subwoofer
which makes it pretty amazing
now a couple of the features that is
fantastic here the back of the system
all right guys so here is the back of
the actual system here you've got your
volume for your speakers on the left and
then you've got your
volume for your subwoofer on the right
and you've got your two xlr inputs here
and then you got your pass-throughs on
here now this speaker also features a
bluetooth setting that you can actually
run any bluetooth device through these
speakers and trust me i've turned it on
i've checked it i've used it
and my phone connects to it every single
time so i had to actually forget it on
my phone so that it'll stop connecting
to it but
every single top also it has an
additional subwoofer out right here now
this input allows you to be able
to run multiple subs at the same time as
you can see there they've got the
display right here that shows you that
you can use this ld sub
as the main sub and then of course your
other one will be considered the slave
sub and trust me this guy packs a mean
punch i've had to turn down the base a
couple of times on these guys because
the cabinet is an all wood cabinet so
none of that plastic here all wood with
a great metal grill on the front
so basically the cabinet and everything
here is housing a 15 inch subwoofer
and it packs so much punch i was not
ready for what the speaker delivered now
a couple of the great features that are
on here as well outside of what's
already on the back are with your
columns so you basically have both of
these and they also supply you with
these styrofoam bottoms that just detach
from the bottom and then they fit right
in here to the top of the subwoofer
so that you can link up both of your
units here now this is actually the top
speaker you can tell it because the top
just has a gap and stuff at the top
there
so the other one
has where you can attach the other
speaker and it has the holes and
everything for you here now this
speakers height is close to seven feet
now i'm six three and this speaker is
taller than i am when i stand up here so
it packs a high range of punch it goes
super tall and you can imagine
getting one of these columns up high
and over the crowd's head so it's not
blaring at them because most people are
less than six feet of course now another
great feature on the back here is what's
considered stereo mode or stereo link
and basically if you have two 44 g2s you
can actually link them
via bluetooth they can link to each
other and then they can play exactly
what the first one has coming off of it
so you don't have to run along cable so
if you want to put one on one side of
the room and the other one on the other
one you should be able to pick up a
signal which connects them without
running an xlr cable pretty dope another
great feature of the speaker has been
the fact that it doesn't receive a lot
of mic input now i've used these at a
couple of settings i use it in a karaoke
setting which was fantastic because that
gave the singer an opportunity to walk
in front of the speaker and the speaker
not wail on them here's an example
[Music]
and you have to excuse the singing
here's an example of a speaker giving a
presentation at a christmas party i want
to give thanks to a number of different
people who have helped pull together
this christmas party kara
there raise your hand thank you
[Applause]
and she has done a marvelous job and so
you see this gives you the option here
to be able to have microphones and stuff
right in front of the speaker if you're
giving that now i'm not going to tell
you that it is perfect it is not i have
had a couple of instances where they
have gotten some feedback
from certain microphones and i'm not
sure if it's just my microphone or if it
was where i was at
but i was not filming at the time so i
don't have a way to show you guys that
but i will tell you that it is not
perfect it does give just a tiny bit of
feedback in certain situations but for
the most part does a great job of
canceling it now some of the additions
that you can pick up to go with the
speakers are the bags and the rolling
cart so let me show you the back of the
actual speaker does not have any type of
way for you to roll this guy out and no
way are we going to sit there and carry
these things back and forth where we
need to go i mean that automatically
eliminates this system from its
simplicity so that's where this guy
comes in
it is a forecaster rolling cart that has
two clamps
right here on either side
for you to be able to clamp to the back
of the speaker and this allows you to be
able to lean the subwoofer back onto the
car
and roll it right out without it
detaching
it also has stoppers on the wheels so
that it will not roll i will tell you
that these things roll on just about
anything every time i've left this on a
flat surface you can kind of see it
moving that stuff just a little bit so
if you're on any type of slope this guy
will roll but this is a wood roller so
it's very sturdy and ready for the
moment and for a quick tutorial on how
you connect this guy to the subwoofer
i've demonstrated that for you check it
out
all right so let me show you guys how to
unhook and hook the
cart
on the back of the ld system
so
you got these knobs here i've already
hooked it on
and you just take these off and it
exposes the whole back so when you're
done
you just make sure the wheels and
everything are turned in twist the other
one on
and voila
so
ld also has
these bags and everything that you could
put it in for easy pack up now remember
none of this stuff comes with it so it
will have to be purchased separately but
let me just show you so on top of having
the styrofoam
the base has to go on the bottom so you
don't damage the post
it's got two dividers on the inside one
for each side of the speaker
and let me show you how that fits in
and then you just fold it over
and you zip it
to the middle
and it has handles on it for you to be
able to carry
moving forward there you go it's got a
nice zippers and stuff on here very well
made this is not a cheap bag by any
means at all
and the subwoofer has a bag as well
again not a cheaply made bag it's got
one pouch for cables
right here in the front
and i've already put my power con cable
that comes with the speakers right in
the front so i never lose them
and it has two handle holes on the side
because there are handles on the side of
the subwoofer so i can tell you that if
you want to level up your system
definitely check out the maui 44 g2 by
ld systems
you will not be disappointed the only
thing that may be a little disappointing
is your pockets this is not a cheap
speaker you are definitely paying for
the quality of this speaker i have
listed a link for you guys to check that
out down below so you can research even
further i would like to thank the good
people over at ld systems for allowing
me to check this out and review it i
have done nothing but love these
speakers and there you have it thank you
guys for watching and we've got more
stuff coming your way stay tuned for
that and if you don't know now you know
see you guys soon
[Music]
you